&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：因为我一直在提出强制的理由，这是其中一件事
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: As I've been making this case for coercion, one of the things that
可能一直浮现在你的脑海里，是的，但是胁迫
may have been floating in the back of your mind is, yeah, but the coercion
我遇到的问题不是加号运算符，也不是if语句。
problem that I have is not with the plus operator, or an if statement.
大多数人似乎都有很大的强制问题
The big coercion problems that most people seem to have
似乎以相等检查为中心。
seem to center around equality checking.
同样的信息，我对所有的胁迫都会申请
And the same message that I have for all of coercion is going to apply for
强制平等。
coercive equality as well.
但我想具体探讨一些关于=对=的问题，
But I wanna dig specifically into some issues about the == versus ===,
因为这真的是大多数人关注的地方
since this is really the place where most people focus their attention
当他们谈论强制的时候。
when they talk about coercion.
事实上，大多数人都没有想过强迫任何其他地方
In fact most people haven't thought about coercion any other place
不同于=与=。
other than the == verse the ===.
所以还有一些进一步的解剖。
So there's some further dissection.
那么你们中有多少人听说过=和之间的区别
So how many of you have heard before that the difference between == and
=检查所谓的松散相等和
=== is that == checks the value so called loose equality and
=检查所谓严格相等类型中的值？
=== checks the value in the type so called strict equality?
这是非常普遍的。
This is extremely common.
不幸的是，尽管听起来真的很好，但事实并非如此。
And unfortunately even though it sounds really good it's not exactly the case.
这不是真正的区别。
That's not exactly the difference.
这不仅仅是学术上的细微差别。
And it's not just an academic nuance here.
这种差异确实改变了我们对公用事业的看法，
The difference really changes our perspective on the utility,
这两种机制在我们的语言中的目的。
the purpose of these two mechanisms in our language.
所以，我真的认为如果你试图理解你的代码，
So, I really think that if you're trying to understand your code,
关键是你要学会像JavaScript一样思考，
it's critical that you learn to think like JavaScript,
这就是论文一直在进行的。
that's sort of been the thesis going along.
同样的道理也适用于双等和三等，也就是说，
And the same is true for double equals and triple equals, that just saying,
嗯，这是一种似乎检查类型，而另一个不检查。
well, it's sort of one seems to check the type and the other doesn't.
这在某些情况下可能会帮你度过难关，但是
That may get you by in some circumstances, but
在其他情况下，它会导致完全不同的结论。
in other circumstances it leads you to completely different conclusions.
与我们所做的所有其他事情都是一致的，让我们看看规范。
So consistent with everything else that we've done, let's look at the spec.
这是规格
This is the spec for
所谓的抽象相等比较，就是双重相等。
what is called abstract equality comparison, which is the double equals.
如果Double Equals仅检查值，而Triple Equals检查值并
And if double equals only checks the value and triple equals checks the value and
类型，那么为什么写在算法的最顶端，
the type, then why write up here at the very top of the algorithm,
非常快的事情，检查x和y的类型了吗？
the very fast thing, are the types of x and y checked?
我们马上就可以揭穿这个神话
Immediately we can debunk the myth
这两者的区别在于类型是否相同。
that the difference between these two is whether the types are the same.
这不是区别。
That isn't the difference.
他们都检查了类型，只是
They both checked the types, it's just that
一个人对这个信息做了一些不同于另一个人的事情，好吗？
one does something different with that information than the other one, okay?
所以第一，正如我们一直说的那样，真理的来源总是规格。
So number 1, the source of truth is always the spec, as we keep saying.
如果你选择坚持不完全正确的心智模式
And if you choose to persist in not completely correct mental models
在某些情况下似乎是有效的，最终时间跨度越长，
that seem to work in some scenarios, eventually the longer the time span goes,
最终你会遇到一个不同的情况，
eventually you'll run into a case where you're in a different scenario,
你的心智模型崩溃了，现在你迷失了。
your mental model is busted, and now you're lost.
我认为最好有一个正确的心智模型。
I think it's better to have the correct mental model.
就像我为您引用的规范的其他地方一样，这是
Just like the other places of the spec that I have cited for you, this is
一种使用if语句和然后语句以及变量和操作的算法。
an algorithm with if statements and then statements and variables and operations.
因此，作为开发人员，您可以理解这一点。
So it's something that you as a developer can understand.
绝大多数JavaScript开发人员从来没有读过这一节。
The vast majority of JavaScript developers have never once read this section.
他们所听到的关于双等号的一切都是这么说的
All they've ever heard about the double equals is what is said
在线关于双等分，在书中有关于双等分的内容。
online about double equals and in books about double equals.
几乎从不引用规范所说的内容。
Which is almost never citing what the spec talks about.
但只是引用了一些轶事证据来解释为什么他们认为这是值得的。
But only citing some anecdotal evidence why they think it's worthy.
所以阅读规范会很有用。
So reading the spec can be useful.
例如，如果我有一个字符串Frank，我已经将它赋给了一个变量，并且
For example, if I have a string, Frank, that I've assigned to one variable, and
然后我创建了另一个副本，本质上，这就是第2行上发生的事情，
then I create another copy, essentially, that's what's happening on line 2,
所以现在我有两条线。
so now I have two strings.
如果在第7行，我试着问这两个是不是相等，就像我在第7行和第8行一样。
And if on line 7 I try to ask if those two are equal, like I am on line 7 and line 8.
在这两种情况下，它们是相等的。
In both cases, they are equal.
因为事实证明，当类型匹配时，它们会执行=。
Because it turns out that when the types match, then they do the ===.
双等于和
The double equals and
当类型匹配时，三元组等于完全相同。
the triple equals are exactly identical when the types match.
绝对没有区别。
There is absolutely no difference.
说明书上是这么说的。
And the spec says so.
当类型匹配时，执行三重等于。
When the types match, do the triple equals.
这就是我刚才为你强调的。
That's what I just highlighted for you.
我们可以在代码中看到这一点。
And we can see that in code.
在值类型已经匹配的任何地方，顺便说一下，如我
In any place where the value types already match, and by the way, as I
已经说了很多次了，你应该试着让值类型变得明显，并且
said a bunch of times already, you should try to have the value types obvious, and
理想情况下，您应该让它们尽可能匹配。
ideally, you should have them matching as much as possible.
这并不意味着你永远不能被强迫，但是
That doesn't mean you can never have coercion, but
你不应该在很多地方做比较。
you shouldn't have lots of places where you're doing comparisons.
你当然不应该做相等的比较和
You certainly shouldn't be doing equality comparisons and
完全不知道类型是什么。
have absolutely no idea what the types are.
对我来说有趣的是，许多人似乎认为这是不可能的
It's interesting to me that many people seem to suggest that it is impossible for
他们编程并了解在这种比较中可能会出现什么类型。
them to program and understand what types could be coming in to this comparison.
我不知道你怎么能在没有某种意义的情况下写出任何算法
And I don't know how you can write any algorithm without having some sense of
这些总是数字，这些总是字符串。
well these are always numbers and these are always strings.
你怎么能说，我不知道？
How can you say, well I have no idea?
它可能是一个数组，它可能是空的。
It could be an array it could be null.
我不知道可能是什么。
I have no idea what it could possibly be.
即使你不知道，这并不意味着它必须保持这种状态。
And even if you don't know, that doesn't mean that it has to stay that way.
您可以选择重新设计代码，以便
You can choose to redesign your code so
你缩小了那些不同种类的地方的表面积
that you've narrowed the surface area of places where those different kinds
类型可以相互匹配，可以相互交织。
of types can intermatch, can interweave with each other.
你已经缩小了那些存在强制的角落案件。
You've narrowed those corner cases that exist with coercion.
所以我不会写一个可以接受NULL，未定义字符串的函数，
So I wouldn't write a function that could take null, undefined string,
Number、Object、Array和14个其他类型，以及
number, object, array, and 14 other types, and
然后所有人都将它们与a=进行比较，这很可笑，对吧？
then all compare them with a ==, that's ludicy, right?
但我会写一个函数，可以接受字符串和数字
But I would write a function that could take strings and numbers and
将它们与a=进行比较。
compare them with a ==.
因为有一个非常有名的
Because there's a very known and
要解决的潜在拐角案例的小子集。
small subset of potential corner cases to work around.
如果你注意的话，这些都是可以避免的。
And those are avoidable if you pay attention.
因此，在类型已经匹配的情况下，=和=是相同的。
So in the case where the types already match, == and === are the same.
那么=在做什么呢？
So what is === doing?
嗯，它也在检查类型，如果它们不相同，它就是假的。
Well, it's also checking the types, and if they're not the same, it's false.
值是什么并不重要，
It doesn't matter what the values are,
如果类型不同，它不做任何其他事情。
if the types are different, it doesn't do anything else.
它有点短路，然后说，
It sorta short-circuits and says,
如果类型不同，它们不可能是相等的。
if the types are different there's no possible way that they could be equal.
如果你考虑一下双等号会做什么，
If you think about that with respect to what double equals is gonna do,
我们一会儿就来看一下。
which we're gonna look at in just a moment.
从本质上讲，严格平等和严格平等之间的真正区别
Essentially the real difference between strict equality and
松散的平等就是我们是否会允许任何强迫的发生。
loose equality is whether or not we're going to to allow any coercion to occur.
那么，如果类型相同，我们严格平等会做什么呢？
So what us Strict Equality is gonna do if the types are the same?
好的，如果他们是nans，就会返回false，
Well it's going to, return false if they're NaNs,
因为记住它应该是关于Nans的谎言。
because remember it's supposed to lie about NaNs.
如果有负零，它将返回真，因为它应该是谎言
And it's gonna return true if there's a negative zero because it's supposed to lie
关于负零。
about negative zeros.
但只有在类型已经匹配的情况下，它才会说谎。
But it only does the lies if the types already match.
否则，它会显示FALSE，并且根本没有检查任何内容。
Otherwise, it says false and it didn't check anything at all.
所以也许更合适的说法是
So maybe the more appropriate statement would be
他们都检查类型，其中一个提前停止，另一个不检查。
that they both check the types one of them stops early and one of them doesn't.
或者换一种方式说，不同的是我们是否允许强迫。
Or said a different way, the difference is whether we allow coercion.
所以在这里，我有两个物体，好吗？
So here, I have two objects, all right?
它们具有相同的结构和表面上相同的价值。
They have the same structure and ostensibly the same value.
但它们不是同一个物体。
But they are not the same object.
它们是两个不同的物体。
They are two different objects.
很多时候人们对JavaScript内置的等式检查感到困惑
A lot of times people get confused with JavaScript's built in equality checking
它在某种程度上不是结构性的，
that it's somehow not structural in nature,
它不像深层断言检查那样
that it doesn't do like a deep assertion check that
一个对象的结构与另一个对象的结构完全相同。
the structure of one object is exactly the same as a structure of another object.
也许有这样的语言，但我不知道
Maybe there are languages like that, but I don't know
这是一种流行的东西，在一种语言中被内置到操作符中。
of that to be a prevailing thing that's built into an operator in a language.
大多数操作员似乎都在做JavaScript所做的事情，即身份比较。
Most operators seem to do what JavaScript does, which is identity comparison.
如果Workshop1和Workshop 2指向字面上相同的对象引用，则
If workshop1 and workshop 2 pointed at literally the same object reference then
他们的身份会是一样的，你就会变成真的。
their identity would be the same and you'd get true.
但在这个特殊的情况下，他们不是平等的，好吗？
But in this particular case, they're not equal, okay?
所以无论=还是=都不会返回真，因为它们是不同的对象。
So neither == nor === is gonna return a true because they are different objects.
大家跟我来？
Everybody follow me?
它们是不同的物体，它们不一样。
They're different objects, they are not the same.
所以你用哪一个并不重要，
And so it doesn't matter which one you use,
你还是会得到同样的结果。
you're still gonna get the same result.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：换句话说，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So in other words,
当类型不同时，=将允许强制。
the == is going to allow coercion when the types were different.
并且当类型相同时，=将不允许强制。
And the === is going to disallow coercion when the types are the same.